



SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

## **EDUCATION**

# School of Visual Arts, BFA New York, NY

# **ABOUT ME**

Senior graphic designer with over 30 years of experience delivering high-quality creative solutions to clients across a wide-range of industries. I live and breathe design and I love using my passion to bring my clients' creative visions to life.

## **SKILLS**

Adobe Creative Suite
PowerPoint
Website Design
CSS
Logo & Brand Design
Editorial Design
Typography
Infographs
Conference Collateral
Interactive PDF

# CONTACT

US: +1 954.850.9119 SE: +46 76.011.21.31

schinkler@hotmail.com RogerAD.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Senior Graphic Designer**

Freelance, Stockholm, Sweden/Fort Lauderdale, FL 2018 - Present

- Collaborate with clients to develop engaging and innovative visual content.
- Design and create websites, logos, print material, PowerPoint presentations, and interactive PDFs.
- Developed collateral for annual conferences, including signage, wall graphics, pull-up banners and badges.
- Produced print material for teachers and students to use as hands-on learning tools.

### **Director of Creative Services**

Airport Revenue News, Fort Lauderdale, FL 2004 - 2018

- Oversaw design projects for leading airport magazine.
- Managed production of monthly print magazine by developing layout and working closely with editorial director and writers to create story visuals.
- Collaborated regularly with sales team to ensure quality visuals and effective messaging in all advertising materials.
- Managed development and production of collateral for company's global annual conference, including large entrance graphics, columns wraps, attendee book, name badges, and lanyards.
- Led development of the North American Airport Fact Book, a 500-page reference book that provided valuable data on airports through clear and compelling visuals.

### **Graphic Designer**

Freelance, New York, NY 1992 - 2004

- Designed and developed websites for clients across various industries.
- Representative clients include BMW, Jaguar, Aston Martin, and Barnes & Noble.